Big man!
Hey, Kel!
Or soda!
It sucks!
Kel,
I think the door not opening
might have something to do with that
big chain that's like around it.
The chain, the chain. Oh, what kind of inhuman
monster would do this, huh?
Look out, Papa.
Chris, Chris, what, some
sicko that put a chain around an orange soda cooler?
Kel, Chris, it's the sicko.
What, what's wrong with you?
Kel, do you know that last month you drank over $100
worth of free orange soda?
Really? I thought it was so much more.
It was plenty!
From now on, if you want orange soda, you'll have to pay for it.
And until you pay up, the chain
stays put.
I ain't gonna, I'll pay you back!
The rules been,
the rules been,
I need orange soda in my life!
If I don't have orange soda, I can't live!
I can't live!
I'll be in the back fussing with my hair.
Kel, you all right?
Whoa!
Whoa! Orange soda!
You can't do this to me! You can't do this to me!
Kel, why don't you just pay for the orange soda?
Yeah, like where am I supposed to get
some money? Oh, if only
I could do things for people in a cave
for money.
You mean like get a job?
Get a job!